Excuse me?
} me, sir?
Oh, come on.
Do you } a moment, sir?
I'm } in the middle of } here.
Yes? Thank you.
I've } a long way for you, Franck.
My name is Victor.
Hi.
And you are....
You are Franck.
You are so much } than just a sheep, aren't you?
Oh yeah? How would you know?
Look at you. You're an }, Franck.
Just }, you're... a lone wolf.
Tell me, does one choose to be }?
No, one doesn't.
One doesn’t even choose to be a wolf.
Or does one?
Well, mister... err... Hector.
Victor. Victor.
I don’t know what you’re on about but I'm just
a sheep minding its own business.
And I suggest you do the same.
No. No no no, Franck. Wait wait wait.
No. This is not... the way.
Just give me } of your precious }.
} time? Hehehe.
Yeah } give me one minute.
You would have one more minute, wouldn't you?
Okay half. Half a minute.
I knew it.
You will not } this.
The adventures you } have.
All the lives you've ever }.
All you’ve been missing.
Here. This is... the best } we have... in store.
Variable spin speed, excellent tumble performance...
...in one... handy... device. Squeaky clean.
Well this... this } be good.
Took me ages to tie that rope.
No more need for hooves.
No more sheepy business.
Ho! Time flies.
Wait wait wait wait wait wait.
How does this thing work?
I mean, how do I make it work?
No you don't.
I just turned it on for you.
When can I go?
Where can I go?
We will pick you up. Don't worry, just stay here.
In this exact place.
Don't move. Just wait.
That's it?
Hey!
Wait, mister!
Eh, Casper!
Hector whatever!